# 大家好 今天我們來到了南昌
Hi everyone! We've arrived at Nanchang today,
# 參加這第十七届中國國際農產品交易會
to participate in the 17th China International Agricultural Trade Fair.
# 就在這裡面 等下我們就進去
It's right over there. We'll be entering immediately.
# 帶大家去看一下
Let's show you around.
# 這個是雞腿還是鴨腿
Is it chicken leg or duck leg?
# 鴨腿 鴨腿 額 對
Duck
Duck?
Eh, yea!
# 那麼長一條
What a long fish!
# 應該夾不到手的哦
I don't think it can pinch my hand.
# 這是 這是公的
It's, it's male.
# 公的這個 這是公的
This is male.
Yea, this is male.
# 公的 哇 好大個的
Male! Wa! It's big!
# 你看 這個是石蛙哦
Look! This is spiny frog.
# 還有娃娃魚
And giant salamanders too.
# 好大條娃娃魚
They're really big.
# 小水魚
These are small softshell turtles.
# 這個叫甲魚苗
These are the young turtles.
# 甲魚苗
The young ones.
# 這個是鱘魚呦
This is sturgeon.
# 好大的鯽魚啊
Huge "ji yue" (local carps).
# 路相通 渠相連 旱能灌 澇能排 (註︰非對白)
Road joined, sewage connected, land irrigated, flood discharged
# 葛根哦 那麼大一條
It's ge gen (Chinese herb). It's so big!
# 哇 這好大的南瓜
Wa! This pumpkin is huge!
# 哇 真的哦
Wa! It's real!
# 鴕鳥蛋 (註︰非對白)
Ostrich eggs
# 中國好柚子(註︰非對白)
Chinese Pamela
# 贛州觀迎你 (註︰非對白)
Welcome to Ganzhou
# 這臍橙好大哦
These navel oranges are really big!
# 很靚 很漂亮
Beautiful! Pretty!
# 贛州臍橙 (註︰非對白)
Ganzhou navel oranges
# 你看
Look!
# 這個都是包菜來的哦
These are all cabbages.
# 那麼小
So small.
# 味道還可以哦
It tastes not too bad.
# 現在閉館啦 我們要回去啦
It's closing, and we need to leave now.
# 我們後天還要去縣裡面
We still need to participate in the navel oranges picking competition
# 那個摘臍橙比賽
in the, in our own county on the day after tomorrow.
# 現在就要回去了
So we're heading back home now.